<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools">

	<string name="app_name">Testland</string>
	<string name="test"> James Gosling received a Bachelor of Science from the University of Calgary [4] and his M.A. and Ph.D. from Carnegie Mellon University, all in computer science.[2][5][6] He wrote a version of Emacs called Gosling Emacs  while working toward his doctorate. He built a multi-processor version of Unix for a 16-way computer system[7] while at Carnegie Mellon University, before joining Sun . He also developed several compilers and mail systems there. </string>
	<string name="test2"> Gosling was with Sun between 1984 and 2010 (26 years). He is known as the father of the Java programming language.[8][9] He got the idea for the Java VM while writing a program to port software from a by translating  Q-Code to VAX assembler and emulating the hardware. He left Sun  on April 2, 2010 after it was acquired by the Oracle Corporation,[8] citing reductions in pay, status, and decision-making ability, along with change of role and ethical challenges. </string>
	<string name="ada_1">Augusta Ada King, Countess of Lovelace (née Byron; 10 December 1815 – 27 November 1852) was an English mathematician and writer, chiefly known for her work on Charles Babbage proposed mechanical general-purpose computer, the Analytical Engine. She was the first to recognise that the machine had applications beyond pure calculation, and published the first algorithm intended to be carried out by such a machine. As a result, she is sometimes regarded as the first to recognise the full potential of a "computing machine" and one of the first computer programmers.[2][3][4]</string>
	<string name="ada_2">Lovelace was the only legitimate child of the poet Lord Byron and his wife Anne Isabella "Annabella" , Lady [5] All of Byron other children were born out of wedlock to other women.[6] Byron separated from his wife a month after Ada was born and left England forever four months later. He commemorated the parting in a poem that begins, "Is thy face like thy mother's my fair child! ADA! sole daughter of my house and heart?".[7]</string>
</resources>
